burf.com 2007-12-16

# Burf.com Alternative Search Engine and Entertainment Portal : Privacy Policy

**OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**

Thank you for visiting Burf.com.

Protecting consumer privacy is very important to us. Our Online Privacy Statement is available to inform you about our collection and use of personal information so that you can make informed choices about how your own information is collected and used. This Online Privacy Statement reflects the Burf.com policies covering personal information collected at this website on or after the effective date shown above.   
**  
COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**  
Burf.com collects personal information in order to offer or provide goods and services to consumers and our customers. We may obtain this information from a variety of sources:

· From website submissions.  
· From transactions in which Burf.com and consumers are involved;  
**  
DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**  
Burf.com does not disclose customer information to third parties.

**WE ARE COMMITTED TO PROTECTING THE CONFIDENTIALITY OF PERSONAL CONSUMER INFORMATION.**  
Burf.com limits access to personal information to those employees of Burf.com who need it to fulfill their business responsibilities.   
Employees must adhere to Burf.com privacy policies. Employees violating these policies may be subject to disciplinary action, up to and including dismissal.   
Vendors and other outside contractors we engage are subject to our contractual requirements to ensure that sensitive personal information is safeguarded.

**WE USE APPROPRIATE SECURITY SAFEGUARDS**.  
At Burf.com, security is a priority. We employ appropriate measures to protect consumer information against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. These may include, among others, encryption, physical access security and other appropriate technologies. Mixcat.com continually reviews and enhances its security systems, as necessary.  
**  
WEBSITE MAY BE LINKED TO OTHER WEBSITES.**  
Burf.com may create links to third party websites. Burf.com is not responsible for the content or privacy practices employed by websites that are linked from our website.

If you have any questions or indeed comments about our Online Privacy Statement,or for some reason believe we have not adhered to our statement, please contact:

E-mail the Burf.com Data Protection Officer: DataProtection@Burf.com

We may alter this statement as needed for certain products and services and to abide by local laws or regulations around the world. Burf.com reserves the right to amend or modify this statement from time to time. We urge you to review this statement whenever you visit in order to obtain the most current statement. You may change your choices at any time.
